<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Search Engine | CyberWalker]]></title>
  <link href="http://gnah.me/blog/categories/search-engine/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://gnah.me/"/>
  <updated>2015-05-30T22:32:39-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://gnah.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Hahn]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Firefox Addon to Quickly Search for Selected Texts]]></title>
    <link href="http://gnah.me/blog/2015/03/03/a-firefox-addon-to-quickly-search-for-selected-texts/"/>
    <updated>2015-03-03T22:55:32-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://gnah.me/blog/2015/03/03/a-firefox-addon-to-quickly-search-for-selected-texts</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>Background</h1>

<p>If you often see something on webpage and want to do a Google search of it, then this addon could be a huge time saver.</p>

<p>It is basically a Firefox addon to quickly search for selected texts on a
     webpage. So you don&rsquo;t have to &ldquo;copy, moving to the search box in the
browser, paste, and hit <code>enter</code>&rdquo;. Instead you can just select the texts and then press
some keyboard shortcuts. This add-on will open up a new tab and show the search engine results.</p>

<p>I used to live without it until one day I had to do some quite intensive searching.
Having to repeatedly following that cumbersome procedure kinda drove me crazy.
So I googled it and it turned out, in this day and age, there isn&rsquo;t a
quick way to do it! Then I decided to write my own. It works quite well and now I
can&rsquo;t live without it.</p>

<p>If you are stilling struggling with this kinda issue, hope this will help you too!</p>

<h1>Usage</h1>

<ol>
<li>Install this <a href="https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/search-selected-shortcuts/">Search Selected Shortcuts addon</a> (no need to restart).</li>
<li>Select the text you want to search on a webpage.</li>
<li>Press some keyboard shortcuts:

<ul>
<li><strong><code>alt + s</code></strong>: google search the selected text</li>
<li><strong><code>alt + q</code></strong>: google search the selected text, but also put them in double quotes.<br/>
 E.g. you&rsquo;ve selected, <code>theory of everything</code>, then it will do a search of <code>"theory of everything"</code></li>
<li><strong><code>alt + c</code></strong>: google search the selected text, but only search in the current site.
 E.g. if you are on <code>stackoverflow.com</code>, the search would be like, <code>hackish site:stackoverflow.com</code></li>
<li><strong><code>alt + i</code></strong>: google image search</li>
<li><strong><code>alt + w</code></strong>: wikipedia search the selected text</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Eureka!</li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
